Free my heart to follow You
Serve in Spirit and in truth
Lord free my spirit to follow You
Give me wisdom to know the truth
Is that your prayer this morning? Lift your hands and bless Him.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Free my heart to follow You
Serve in Spirit and in truth
Lord free my spirit to follow You
Give me wisdom to know the truth
Holy Spirit free me
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Free my heart to follow You
Free my spirit to chase after You
Serve in Spirit and in truth
Lord free my spirit to follow You
Give me wisdom to know the truth
Let us sing together
Lord free my heart to follow You
Serve in Spirit and in truth
Lord free my spirit to follow You
Give me wisdom to know the truth
Holy Spirit free me
Free my heart to follow You
We gonna be free
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you for your freedom!
Holy Spirit, thank you for your freedom!
Holy Spirit free me
Free my heart to follow You
TT: 28/03/19 Esther Mwelwa
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 07/04/2019